Guide to the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records
1902-2014
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5739
International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers.$bLocal 46 (Seattle, Wash.)
47.17 cubic feet (51 boxes) and 2 oversized folders
Records of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46
The International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers was founded in St. Louis, Missouri in 1890, when a group of electrical workers got together and chartered the National Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 5221 under the leadership of its first president, Henry Miller. Local 217 of Seattle, Washington was established in 1901 and ordered defunct in 1908. For six years, dissenting forces within the union caused a split, with each side electing its own officers. The AFL ultimately deemed the McNulty-Collins faction as the legitimate brotherhood. In 1914, the IBEW Local 46 was formed in Seattle with a membership of 250 men of various occupations: inside wiremen, marine wiremen, radio workers and telephone operators that worked in shipyards, industrial areas, uptown Seattle and its vicinity. Over the years the departments of the IBEW grew to include Sound and Communication, Residential, Marine, HVAC, Electronics, Motor Shop, Neon Sign and Maintenance. Current Local 46 jurisdiction includes King, Kitsap, Jefferson and Clallam Counties. Today, Local 46 is composed of over 4,500 members in a variety of craft units as well as over 1200 associate members.
Organized into 2 accessions.
Accession No. 5739-001, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1910-2009
Accession No. 5739-002, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1902-2014
This collection documents the various activities of several branches of International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 46 located in the Seattle, Washington and its surrounding areas. The bulk of the collection contains papers that originated in the Seattle branch 46 of the IBEW, as well as documents that were collected at the time of its creation as well as through subsequent mergers. The documents are from the various committees and units of Local 46, as well as some geographical offshoots of Local 46. The collection details the activities of the Union and its members, as well as the relations between the Union and employers.
Open to all users.
The visual materials that form part of this collection are described and indexed in the guide to the
.
International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers.$bLocal 46 (Seattle, Wash.)$vArchives; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Electricians$xLabor unions$zWashington (State)$zSeattle$vArchives
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Washington (State)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1910-2009; 5739-001; 26.52 cubic feet 31 boxes
  The collection is arranged into 7 series.
  Series I: Membership Records & Dues
  Series II: Meeting Minutes & Registers
  Series III: Contract Negotiations
  Series IV: Office Files
  Series V: Financial Records
  Series VI: Education/Training
  Series VII: Publications & Reports
  Membership Records & Dues (Series I), Meeting Minutes & Registers (Series II) and Publications and Reports (Series VII) are arranged according to originating body. Contract Negotiations (Series III), Office Files (Series IV), Financial Records (Series V) and Education/Training (Series VI) are arranged by function. Within these subseries, files are arranged chronologically by date of the oldest document in the file. Contract Negotiations (Series III) is arranged alphabetically within the subseries.
  The largest part of the collection is the Meeting Minutes & Registers (Series II), which document the issues most pertinent to the Union and its members. Another large portion of the collection is Contract Negotiations (Series III), which showcases the evolvement of contracts, and workers rights as a whole, over time. Of particular note are the files involving the IBEW Local 46’s correspondence and negotiations with KIRO Incorporated and Fisher Broadcasting Incorporated, which offer insight into discord between employers, employees and the union. The day-to-day workings of the IBEW can be assessed from Membership Records & Dues (Series I), Office Files (Series IV), Financial Records (Series V) and Education/Training (Series VI). In addition, Publications & Reports (Series VII) offers some more general union information as found in serial publications.
  View selections from this accession in digital format
  Open to all users.
  - Series I: Membership Records & Dues, 1930-1983 (Box-folder 1/1-1/3; 2/1-2/3; 3/1-3/3; 4/1; 4/6; 5/2-5/4)
    Series I includes detailed Membership Records & Dues for the general membership of Local 46 from 1930-1945, as well as a handful of departmental Membership Records & Dues. The series also includes Application Fees and Permit Hands related to the membership records of the late 1930s to early 1940s.
    View selections from this collection in digital format
    The series is subdivided by originating body: Subseries A: General Membership Records & Dues; Subseries B: Business Agent Membership Records; Subseries C: A Member Records; Subseries D: Seattle Building Fund Membership Records & Dues; Subseries E: Application Fees; Subseries F: Permit Hands. Subseries A: General Membership Records & Dues is further arranged chronologically.
    - Subseries A: General Membership Records & Dues, 1930-1945 (Box-folder 1/1-1/3; 2/1-2/3; 3/1-3/3)
      - Membership Records & Dues, January 1930-December 1931 (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Membership Records & Dues, January 1932-March 1934 (Box-folder ½)
      - Membership Records & Dues, November 1937-September 1939 (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Membership Records & Dues, August 1941-August 1942 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Membership Records & Dues, April 1942-July 1942 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Membership Records & Dues, July 1942-October 1942 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Membership Records & Dues, September 1942-June 1943 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Membership Records & Dues, July 1943-February 1944 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Membership Records & Dues, August 1944-February 1945 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Subseries B: Business Agent Membership Records, September 1941-June 1983 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Subseries C: A Member records, September 1951-February 1966 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Subseries D: Seattle Building Fund Membership Records & Dues, February 1945-September 1949 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Subseries E: Application Fees, November 1937-December 1941 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Subseries F: Permit Hands, July 1939-May 1941 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Series II: Meeting Registers & Minutes, 1910-1997 (Box-folder 6/1-6/16; 7/1-7/6; 7/8; 8/1-8/16; 9/1-9/7; 10/1-10/7; 11/1-11/8; 12/1-12/14; 13/1-13/11; 14/1-14/11; 15/1-15/9)
    Series II includes extensive minutes for Local 46 and it’s numerous departments. The General Meeting Minutes and Executive Board Meeting Minutes are complete and span from the 1920s-1970s. The bulk of the other departmental minutes are from the 1950s-1980s.
    The series is subdivided by the originating departmental body within Local 46: Subseries A: General Board Meeting Minutes Local 217; Subseries B: General Board Meeting Minutes Local 46; Subseries C: Executive Board Meeting Minutes Local 46; Subseries D: Joint Executive Board Minutes Local 46 and Local 77; Subseries E: Retired Members Club of IBEW Meeting Minutes; Subseries F: Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes; Subseries G: Marine Unit Meeting Minutes; Subseries H: Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes; Subseries I: E.F.E. Unit Meeting Minutes; Subseries J: Manufacturing Unit Meeting Minutes; Subseries K: Motor Shop Unit Meeting Minutes; Subseries L: N.Y.E. Systems Unit Meeting Minutes; Subseries M: Port Angeles Unit Meeting Minutes; Subseries N: Bremerton Unit Meeting Register & Minutes; Subseries O: Broadcast Unit Meeting Register & Minutes; Subseries P: Cranemen Local 241 Meeting Minutes; Subseries Q: Neon/Electrical Sign Unit Meeting Register & Minutes; Subseries R: Oil Burner Unit Meeting Register & Minutes; Subseries S: Electronics Unit Meeting Register & Minutes; Subseries T: Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes. Each subseries is further arranged chronologically
    - Subseries A: General Meeting Minutes Local 217, November 1910-October 1911 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Subseries B: General Meeting Minutes Local 46, 1918-1976 (Box-folder 6/2-6/16; 7/1-7/6)
      - General Meeting Minutes, January 1918-September 1918 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - General Meeting Minutes, October 1918-September 1919 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - General Meeting Minutes, July 1920-July 1921 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - General Meeting Minutes, July 1921-May 1922 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - General Meeting Minutes, May 1922-March 1923 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - General Meeting Minutes, September 1924-May 1925 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - General Meeting Minutes, May 1925-December 1925 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - General Meeting Minutes, December 1925-August 1926 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - General Meeting Minutes, August 1926-May 1927 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - General Meeting Minutes, May 1927-June 1928 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - General Meeting Minutes, June 1928-October 1929 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - General Meeting Minutes, November 1929-March 1932 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - General Meeting Minutes, September 1930-November 1930 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - General Meeting Minutes, November 1932-March 1937 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - General Meeting Minutes, March 1937-September 1941 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - General Meeting Minutes, November 1941-October 1946 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - General Meeting Minutes, November 1946-December 1951 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - General Meeting Minutes, January 1952-June 1957 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - General Meeting Minutes, July 1957-September 1961 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - General Meeting Minutes, October 1961-March 1967 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - General Meeting Minutes, April 1967-February 1976 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Subseries C: Executive Board Meeting Minutes Local 46, 1921-1975 (Box-folder 8/1-8/16; 9/1-9/6)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, October 1921-July 1923 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, January 1928-March 1931 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, March 1931-August 1933 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, August 1933-May 1935 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, May 1935-April 1942 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Executive Board Notes, September 1936-February 1941 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, January 1938-October 1938 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, May 1942-September 1944 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, September 1944-August 1947 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, August 1947-November 1950 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, November 1950-May 1953 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, May 1953-July 1955 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, July 1955-April 1958 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, May 1958-July 1960 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, July 1960-September 1962 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, September 1962-April 1964 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, May 1964-October 1965 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, November 1965-March 1967 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, April 1967-January 1969 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, January 1969-February 1971 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, March 1971-May 1973 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, May 1973-April 1975 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Subseries D: Joint Executive Board Minutes Local 46 and Local 77, August 1929-March 1950 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Subseries E: Retired Members Club of IBEW Meeting Minutes, March 1968-December 1973 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Subseries F: Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, 1951-1996 (Box-folder 10/1-10/7; 11/1)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, November 1951-January 1957 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, January 1957-July 1961 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, August 1961-May 1966 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, May 1966-December 1975 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, January 1976-December 1982 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, January 1983-March 1988 (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, April 1988-December 1992 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Wireman's Unit Meeting Minutes, January 1993-October 1996 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Subseries G: Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, 1951-1973 (Box-folder 11/2-11/8)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, February 1951-July 1954 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, July 1954-June 1958 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, July 1958-June 1960 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, July 1960-April 1963 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, May 1963-February 1966 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, March 1966-February 1969 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Marine Unit Meeting Minutes, March 1969-February 1973 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Subseries H: Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes, 1948-1976 (Box-folder 12/1-12/7)
      - Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes, April 1948-December 1956 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes, January 1957-August 1962 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes, September 1962-July 1965 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes, July 1965-March 1968 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes, April 1968-February 1971 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes, March 1971-January 1974 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Building Fund Managers Meeting Minutes, January 1974-December 1976 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Subseries I: E.F.E. Unit Meeting Minutes, April 1966-August 1968 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Subseries J: Manufacturing Unit Meeting Minutes, February 1957-July 1958 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Subseries K: Motor Shop Unit Meeting Minutes, 1937-1971 (Box-folder 12/10-12/12)
      - Motor Shop Unit Meeting Minutes, November 1937-April 1940 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Motor Shop Unit Meeting Minutes, March 1951-September 1956 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Motor Shop Unit Meeting Minutes, October 1956-August 1971 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Subseries L: N.Y.E. Systems Unit Meeting Minutes, October 1967-October 1970 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Subseries M: Port Angeles Unit Meeting Minutes, September 1951-July 1957 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Subseries N: Bremerton Unit Meeting Register & Minutes, 1964-1981 (Box-folder 13/1-13/2)
      - Bremerton Unit #9 Meeting Register, April 1964-November 1981 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Bremerton Unit #9 Meeting Minutes, April 1964-September 1975 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Subseries O: Broadcast Unit Meeting Register & Minutes, 1968-1996 (Box-folder 13/3-13/4)
      - Broadcast Unit Meeting Register, October 1968-September 1996 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Broadcast Unit Meeting Minutes, October 1968-June 1982 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Subseries P: Cranemen Local 241 Meeting Minutes, April 1917-April 1919 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Subseries Q: Neon/Electrical Sign Unit Meeting Register & Minutes, 1940-1982 (Box-folder 13/6-13/11)
      - Neon Sign Unit Meeting Register, July 1951-December 1982 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Neon Sign Unit Meeting Minutes, January 1940-May 1950 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Neon Sign Unit Meeting Minutes, July 1950-December 1959 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Electrical Sign and Display Unit Meeting Minutes, January 1960-April 1966 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Electrical Sign and Display Unit Meeting Minutes, May 1966-August 1976 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Electrical Sign and Display Unit Meeting Minutes, October 1976-November 1982 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Subseries R: Oil Burner Unit Meeting Register & Minutes, 1951-1975 (Box-folder 14/1-14/5)
      - Oil Burner Unit Meeting Register, July 1955-November 1967 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Oil Burner Unit Meeting Minutes, March 1951-October 1957 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Oil Burner Unit Meeting Minutes, January 1958-July 1964 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Oil Burner Unit Meeting Minutes, August 1964-December 1969 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Oil Burner Unit Meeting Minutes, January 1970-October 1975 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Subseries S: Electronics Unit Meeting Register & Minutes, 1947-1989 (Box-folder 14/6-14/11)
      - Electronics Unit Meeting Register, October 1977-December 1989 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Radio Unit Meeting Minutes, May 1947-February 1951 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Radio, T.V. & Appliance Unit Meeting Minutes, March 1951-March 1956 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Radio, T.V., Appliance & Sound Unit Meeting Minutes, April 1956-January 1962 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - Electronics Unit Meeting Minutes, February 1962-May 1967 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Electronics Unit Meeting Minutes, June 1967-June 1976 (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Subseries T: Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, 1923-1997 (Box-folder 15/1-15/9)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, February 1923-October 1930 (Box-folder 15/1)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, November 1930-December 1938 (Box-folder 15/2)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, January 1939-March 1947 (Box-folder 15/3)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, April 1947-October 1955 (Box-folder 15/4)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, November 1955-July 1964 (Box-folder 15/5)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, August 1964-September 1972 (Box-folder 15/6)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, October 1972-March 1981 (Box-folder 15/7)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, April 1981-July 1989 (Box-folder 15/8)
      - Electrical Workers Benefit Association Meeting Minutes, August 1989-May 1997 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Series III: Contract Negotiations, 1950-2009 (Box-folder 16/1-16/47; 17/1-17/61; 18/1-18/40; 19/1-19/43; 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
    Series III includes contracts and letters of assent between Local 46 and its numerous contracted companies, as well as correspondence, benefit bonds and voting records that relate to contract negotiations. In addition there are grievances filed by union members and employers, National Labor Relations Board cases and settlements made with Local 46 that exemplify the ongoing disputes that occurred when employers and/or union members failed to live up to the contract expectations.
    The series is divided into two subseries based on the distinctly different parts of the office in which each set of files was located: Subseries A: Contract Negotiations Part 1; Subseries B: Contract Negotiations Part 2. It is unclear why the office chose to divide them this way. Within each subseries files are arranged alphabetically. Many of the files in Subseries B: Contract Negotiations Part 2 have a departmental label (Inside Wire; Residential; Stockmen; Sound & Communication, etc.) in parentheses after the company name.
    - Subseries A: Contract Negotiations Part I, 1950-1991 (Box-folder 16/1-16/47; 17/1-17/61; 18/1-18/40; 19/1-19/43)
      - Holmes Electric Contract Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16/1)
      - KIRO, Incorporated - Radio Station KIRO Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1965-1983 (Box-folder 16/2)
      - KIRO, Incorporated - Radio Station KIRO Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1965-1983 (Box-folder 16/3)
      - KIRO, Incorporated - Radio Stations KIRO and KSEA-FM Contract Negotiations, 1986 (Box-folder 16/4)
      - KIRO, Incorporated - Radio Stations KIRO and KSEA-FM Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box-folder 16/5)
      - KIRO Incorporated - KIRO TV Contract Negotiations, Part 1/3, 1964-1983 (Box-folder 16/6)
      - KIRO Incorporated - KIRO TV Contract Negotiations, Part 2/3, 1964-1983 (Box-folder 16/7)
      - KIRO Incorporated - KIRO TV Contract Negotiations, Part 3/3, 1964-1983 (Box-folder 16/8)
      - KIRO Incorporated - KIRO TV Contract Negotiations, 1985 (Box-folder 16/9)
      - KIRO Incorporated - KIRO TV Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16/10)
      - KIRO Incorporated - KIRO TV Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16/11)
      - K.J.M. Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 16/12)
      - Fisher Broadcasting Incorporated - KOMO Radio Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1965-1985 (Box-folder 16/13)
      - Fisher Broadcasting Incorporated - KOMO Radio Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1965-1985 (Box-folder 16/14)
      - Fisher Broadcasting Incorporated - KOMO-TV Contract Negotiations, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 16/15)
      - Fisher Broadcasting Incorporated - KOMO-TV Contract Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 16/16)
      - Fisher Broadcasting Incorporated - KOMO-TV Contract Negotiations, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16/17)
      - Kona Electric Contract Negotiations, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 16/18)
      - Lakeside Electric, Incorporated F/K/A ABC Electric Contract Negotiations, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 16/19)
      - Lakeway Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1983 (Box-folder 16/20)
      - Lake Union Dry Dock Company Contract Negotiations, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 16/21)
      - Lake Washington School District No. 414 Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 16/22)
      - Lake Washington School District No. 414 Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 16/23)
      - Lander Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1962-1985 (Box-folder 16/24)
      - C. Lane Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 16/25)
      - Larry's Electric Contract Negotiations, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 16/26)
      - W. D. Lasater Company Contract Negotiations, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 16/27)
      - Lent's Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1965-1984 (Box-folder 16/28)
      - Lightning Electric Contractors, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 16/29)
      - Lindberg Electric Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 16/30)
      - Lindsey Electric Contract Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16/31)
      - Lloyd Electric Apparatus Company Contract Negotiations, 1974; 1988 (Box-folder 16/32)
      - Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction Company Contract Negotiations, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 16/33)
      - Loh's Electric, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 16/34)
      - L. O. M., Inc. F/K/A Mid City Electric Contract Negotiations, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 16/35)
      - Lord Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1968-1986 (Box-folder 16/36)
      - Lunde Electric Company, Incorporated Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974; 1990 (Box-folder 16/37)
      - Harry C. Lynde Company D/B/A Wor-Ell Custom Lighting Contract Negotiations, 1957-1981 (Box-folder 16/38)
      - Maltby Construction Contract Negotiations, 1985 (Box-folder 16/39)
      - Maple Valley Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1965-1986 (Box-folder 16/40)